OK, so let's start by defining the J Query handler.
And we'll define it here.
And we'll say, Jake, where we get handler.
Is requested when accessing the Web page.
And the perimeter RFQ.
Is the request for which the you are right needs to be handled?
And the return is ESP, OK?
And this will be static and returns espérer type.
And it's the Jake Query Handler, which takes a pointer to the HPD request structure.
And call it RFQ.
And the HPD request data structure holds all the information for the request.
OK, so here, lug a message.
That says Jake Query requested.
And then the response type using a speedy response set type.
Which takes the request.
And the tape is application slash JavaScript.
And if you follow the function definition.
You'll find that there are some commonly used types to find here, but we'll use others in addition
to these as well.
OK, so next, we'll send the response using HPD, underscore response, underscore send and past the
request, then the constant sharp pointer type.
So we can pass the joke where we start.
And then passed the J Query end.
Minus the start.
And if we follow the function definition.
You'll see that here.
We're just passing the request.
The buffer and the buffer length.
OK, so then just return ESP, OK.
All right, so now let's define the next handler by copying this one.
And pasting it beneath.
And to you will update the comment by saying, since the index, that HTML page.
And then just come down and grab the handler.
So that we can update the function name.
And then just change this to index that HTML.
And then we'll set the type as text H.M..
And then let's copy the HTML start and give it as the buffer.
And the length will take the H.M. end to complete the length parameter, and that's it.
So now let's keep going and copy.
And then paste it again.
And then update the comment.
To say app access.
And then I'll just fix this here and up here as well.
So we'll get the function name.
And place it here.
And then update the log message.
And then we can grab the KSAZ start.
And then we can also take care of the end as well right here.
And then also, we should remember to update the type as well.
Which is CSIS, so we can say.
Text forward slash CSIS.
OK, so let's let's keep it moving.
Let's just do the same.
And then he will do the duchess.
All right, so now let's just get the function name.
Place it here.
And update the message.
And the Typekit, that's fine.
So let's get the app just start.
And update the Senate function.
OK, that looks good.
OK, let's let's do the last one.
And you will say since the day that I come.
Icon.
File when accessing the Web page.
So let's update the function name.
Place it.
Then log the message.
And the type you that will be image slash x dash icon.
So now get the favicon start.
And we can update the response.
OK.
That's it.
So at this point, we can call the 8TB server start function.
They can do that by heading over to the Wi-Fi app that see.
Uncomment the function call.
And that looks good.
So build the project.
And let's just give it a minute.
OK, then now let's flesh.
OK, then let's open a serial monitor here.
And we can see that the Web server has started.
Now we can connect to the ESP.
And now let's open up Google Chrome.
And then navigate to our IP, which is one nine two one six eight zero, that one and hit enter.
Greg, the Web server responds with a Web page.
Great.
Everything looks good.
And on the monitor, our handler messages are logged for the HTML.
Jake Query, CSS and JavaScript, and also the five con Echo as well.
And this icon that shows up right here.
And the select button already has the JavaScript functionality to select the bin file.
And the update firmware button also reacts via the JavaScript functions included in the template files.
All right, so that's all for now, and the next lesson will continue to expand the web server.